(Amy:)Okay, I'm starting
to feel guilty.
(Amy:)Aren't we being a little mean?
(Raj:)That's a fair point.
(Raj:)We wouldn't make fun of someone
like this to their face.
Look, it's Stuart!
(Raj:)You may want
to leave the room.
SHELDON:
Right this way, Uncle Harvey.
(Leonard:)Will you stop with that already?
(Howard:)I'm trying
not to attract attention.
(Leonard:)And tipping his hat to the
cleaning lady didn't do that?
She said, “Buenas noches.”
What was he supposed to do?
(Leonard:)Let's just start
the experiment.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, we should probably
have our story straight
(Sheldon:)in case we get caught.
(Leonard:)We're not getting caught.
(Sheldon:)Well, you can't be sure of that.
(Sheldon:)What if the helium dealer
rats us out?
(Sheldon:)What if Kripke asks
where we got it?
(Sheldon:)What if the university
checks my family tree